Marzet Khatit

Junior Frontend Developer

I'm a junior frontend developer with a strong background of over four years in IT support and a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology. My professional experience includes technical support, telephone customer care, conflict resolution, problem solving. Helping end users with software and troubleshooting network issues. During my internship and coursework I made a commercial website along with my fellow student. Last year I got "Responsive web design" certificate. I am currently working in tech support part-time and learning JavaScript by myself with online courses and websites. I believe that my skills and experience make me an excellent candidate for the frontend developer position.

marzet.rock@gmail.com +79385153368 https://www.linkedin.com/in/marzet/ https://stairwaytohell.github.io/

Work experience

Technical Support Specialist

Service-partner, Krasnodar, RU (from 11/2018 to Present – 1 year) IT support for food retail company

Webmaster

Freelance, Krasnodar, RU (from 06/2015 to 10/2018 – 3 years 10 months) Websites content and HTML/CSS code editor

Technical Support Specialist

Transcard System, Krasnodar, RU (06/2016 to 03/2018 – 1 year 10 months)

IT support for Internet service provider

Intern

Kuban State University, Krasnodar, RU (12/2014 to 07/2015 – 8 months) Internship and thesis

Technical Support Specialist

Rostelecom, Krasnodar, RU (10/2013 to 12/2014 – 1 year 3 months) IT support for Internet service provider

Education

Kuban State University (2010 to 2015) Bachelor's degree Information Systems and Technology

Certifications

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp, Issued Dec 2018

Skills

Responsive Web Design, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Technical Support

Languages

Russian (Bilingual proficiency)
Adyghe (Bilingual proficiency)
English (Professional working proficiency)